<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="urn:x-suse:xslt:profiling:docbook51-profile.xsl"
 type="text/xml"
 title="Profiling step"?>
<!DOCTYPE chapter [
 <!ENTITY % entities SYSTEM "entities.ent"> %entities;
]>
<!---->
<chapter xmlns="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xml:id="alarm_explorer">
 <title>Alarm Explorer</title>
 <para>
  This page displays the alarms for all services and appliances. By default,
  alarms are sorted by their state.
 </para>
 <section>
  <title>Filter and Sort</title>
  <para>
   Using the <guibutton>Filter Alarms</guibutton> button, you can filter the
   alarms by their IDs and dimensions. The <guimenu>Filter Alarms</guimenu>
   dialog lets you configure a filtering rule using the <guimenu>Alarm
   ID</guimenu> field and options in the <guimenu>Dimension(s)</guimenu>
   section.
  </para>
  <para>
   You can display the alarms by grid, list or table views by selecting the
   corresponding icons next to the <guimenu>Sort By</guimenu> control.
  </para>
  <para>
   To sort the alarm list, click on the desired column header. To reverse the
   sort order click again on the column.
  </para>
 </section>
 <section>
  <title>Alarm Table</title>
  <para>
   Each row has a checkbox to allow you to select multiple alarms and set the
   same condition on them.
  </para>
  <para>
   The <emphasis role="bold">Status</emphasis> column displays a graphical
   indicator that shows the state of each alarm:
  </para>
  <itemizedlist>
   <listitem>
    <para>
     Green square (or green indicator): OK. Good operating state.
    </para>
   </listitem>
   <listitem>
    <para>
     Yellow diamond (or yellow indicator): Warning. Low severity, not requiring
     immediate action.
    </para>
   </listitem>
   <listitem>
    <para>
     Red dot (or red indicator): Alarm. Varying severity levels and must be
     addressed.
    </para>
   </listitem>
   <listitem>
    <para>
     Gray square (or gray indicator): Unknown.
    </para>
   </listitem>
  </itemizedlist>
  <para>
   The <emphasis role="bold">Alarm</emphasis> column identifies the alarm by
   the name it was given when it was originally created.
  </para>
  <para>
   The <emphasis role="bold">Last Check</emphasis> column displays the date and
   time the most recent occurrence of the alarm.
  </para>
  <para>
   The <emphasis role="bold">Dimension</emphasis> column describes the
   components to check in order to clear the alarm.
  </para>
 </section>
</chapter>
